Honour the Regars Gets of Main Modesty Council for Tuesday, September 16th, 2020 by
Number two,
Rocklamation, Recognizing, Stephen Fleming, Jeff Harris,
Owen Hartman, Patty McOwnick, Danny Overfield, and Jeremy J. Owen,
Fuller Military Service.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Double.
Hi.
Barnes, five.
Jones, hi.
East.
Hi.
Parker.
Five.
Three, Proclamation, Recognizing.
I'll say the Councilwoman, Gallagones,
for her military troops.
Thank you.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Double.
Hi.
East, Step.
Jones, hi.
Barnes, hi.
Or maybe I should have stayed for that?
Yes.
Probably.
I'll have stayed.
I do approve.
But it's for the record.
Let's go ahead and think.
So we're going to picture now in the front.
Oh.
It's all the proclamation.
But these are for you guys, right?
Yeah.
I'm going to think, yes.
Me too.
Parker.
Hi.
I thought I did.
Yes.
Thanks.
Thank you, Parker.
for a book that's scheduled personal prensives.
We have five lines list.
Precious.
Postal.
Aye.
Thank you.
Postal.
Aye.
Six minutes from the second to twenty-five.
Reglar meeting.
Postal.
I was always good to be here.
Just a few things I want to update you on.
We've got a lot that we're working on right now.
Fortunately not everything we can talk about at this point in time,
but there are some exciting things in the work.
I know Tyler and Mayor Parker,
who represent the city on our board.
There are a lot of the things that we're doing on.
Working on, but a couple of things before I do that,
I just want to talk a little bit about why we did the
proclamations tonight.
So every year, the River Bottom Sportsman,
along with the Mid-American Chapter of the Paralyzed Veterans of America,
the host, what we call the Great Dear Hot.
It's an annual outdoor recreational activity for disabled,
paralyzed veterans, and local veteran.
And so we're very excited about the hunters
that we have participating this year,
including our very own council member, Kyle Jones.
We'll be participating this year.
We're very excited about that.
I gave each one of you a schedule of events,
so that you know what's going on.
We do want to remind you that all of the meals
are open to the public.
You're welcome to come and join us,
especially on Friday.
That's the big fish fry and everything else we do on that Friday.
But the hunt this year runs October 29th through November 1st.
The hunters arrive on the 29th.
The opening ceremony is on the 9 a.m.
A Commerce High School gymnasium on the 30th.
And then the activities will run, like I said, through Saturday.
And if we need it, we leave Sunday open.
If we still have some veterans who are participating
that happen to harvest it yet,
we do have that one extra day to make that happen.
But we feel pretty confident.
We've got a good field general out there this year.
Jody Francisco runs the field operations.
We're excited about the spots that we have set up.
We anticipate everyone harvesting early.
We actually added an extra hunt this year.
So normally every veteran used to make four hunts.
They do a morning and afternoon on Friday and Saturday.
We actually added an extra one on Thursday afternoon.
So you have five opportunities this year and a set of four.
So we're pretty excited about that.
We're also pretty excited that Thursday night.
All of this by the way takes place at Jack's house on the dial room.
We'll form in the barn.
Thursday night October 30th.
We're going to be ready.